Privacy
=======

We at Guilded know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways. 

Remember that your use of Guilded’s Services is at all times subject to the [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/privacy), which incorporates this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/terms).

**What does this Privacy Policy cover?**

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services, but not to the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services, including to personalize, provide, and improve our services, to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you and allow other users to contact you, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to analyze how you use the Services. In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties, but only as described below.

As noted in the [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/terms), we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at support@guilded.gg.

**Will Guilded ever change this Privacy Policy?**

We’re constantly trying to improve our Services, so we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well, but we will alert you to changes by placing a notice on the Services, by sending you an email, and/or by some other means. Please note that if you’ve opted not to receive legal notice emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been posted, that means you agree to all of the changes.

**What information does Guilded collect?**

_Information You Provide to Us:_

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, through the registration process and/or through your account settings, we may collect Personal Information such as your email address and third-party account credentials (for example, your log-in credentials for Facebook, Discord or other third party sites). If you provide your third-party account credentials to us or otherwise sign in to the Services through or from a third party site or service, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy; for example, your Discord account username and profile picture may be transferred over to Guilded. Certain information may be required to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features.

We may communicate with you if you’ve provided us the means to do so. For example, if you’ve given us your email address, we may send you promotional email offers on behalf of other businesses, or email you about your use of the Services. If you do not want to receive communications from us, please indicate your preference by contacting us at support@guilded.gg.

_Information Collected Automatically_

Whenever you interact with our Services, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser or device, which may include your IP address, geolocation data, device identification, “cookie” information, the type of browser and/or device you’re using to access our Services, and the page or feature you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your browser or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features. If you click on a link to a third party website or service, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. Again, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties, and we aren’t responsible for their privacy policies and practices. Please be aware that cookies placed by third parties may continue to track your activities online even after you have left our Services, and those third parties may not honor “Do Not Track” requests you have set using your browser or device.

We may use this data to customize content for you that we think you might like, based on your usage patterns. We may also use it to improve the Services - for example, this data can tell us how often users use a particular feature of the Services, and we can use that knowledge to make the Services interesting to as many users as possible.

_Information Collected From Other Websites and Do Not Track Policy_

Through cookies we place on your browser or device, we may collect information about your online activity after you leave our Services. Just like any other usage information we collect, this information allows us to improve the Services and customize your online experience, and otherwise as described in this Privacy Policy. Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. When you turn on the Do Not Track function in your browser, we stop collecting the information from your browser that allows us to tailor advertisements and other content specifically to you that is based on your visits to our advertising partners’ websites. Specifically, we stop collecting information from the unique browser cookie that links your browser to visits to third party sites. Do Not Track signals are set on a browser-by-browser basis, so you must set them on every browser you use if you do not wish to be tracked. Remember that this is just our Do Not Track policy, and we can’t and don’t make any promises about how third parties react when you set this signal on your browser.

**Will Guilded share any of the Personal Information it receives?**

We do not rent or sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone, except as expressly provided below. We may share your Personal Information with third parties as described below:

**Information That’s Been De-Identified:** We may de-identify your Personal Information so that you are not identified as an individual, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners (or allow partners to collect that information from you), who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. However, we never disclose aggregate usage or de-identified information to a partner (or allow a partner to collect such information) in a manner that would identify you as an individual.

**Affiliated Businesses:** In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell or provide products or services to you through or in connection with the Services (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information to your Services profile or to automatically transmit information in your Services profile to your third party account; for example, your Discord account username and profile picture may be transferred over to Guilded. YouTube is another example of a service where cookies or similar technologies may be used to automatically transmit your information from your Services profile to your third party account.  The collection, transfer, storage, and use of your information to Google will be governed by the Google privacy policy, which can be found at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy). We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business’ or websites’ policies.

**Our Agents:** We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you; for example, if you ever purchase anything on Guilded, we may use a payment processing company to receive and process your credit card transactions for us. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

**User Profiles and Submissions:** Certain user profile information, including your name, location, and any video or image content that such user has uploaded to the Services, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Services or address your request for our services. Your account privacy settings may allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Please remember that any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available, and can be collected and used by anyone. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Services and other users can contact you through messages and comments.

**Business Transfers:** We may choose to buy or sell assets, and may share and/or transfer customer information in connection with the evaluation of and entry into such transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

**Protection of Guilded and Others:** We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/terms) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Guilded, our employees, our users, or others.

**Is Personal Information about me secure?**

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but unfortunately, we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

**What Personal Information can I access?**

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us: 

*   username
    
*   email address
    
*   third-party account credentials (for example, Blizzard/Battle.net tag)
    
*   user profile information, including images and videos you have uploaded to the site

The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Services change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at support@guilded.gg

If you are a parent or guardian of a user of our Services who is under 13, you may contact us at any time to ask that (a) we stop collecting Personal Information from such user, (b) we delete any Personal Information already collected from such user, and (c) we stop disclosing Personal Information collected from such user to third parties, but continue to allow for collection and use of Personal Information collected from such user in connection with the Services. Please note that the terms regarding deleted data outlined below in “What choices do I have?” also apply to deleted Personal Information from children under 13.

**What choices do I have?**

You can always opt not to disclose information to us, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features.

You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. Some information may remain in our records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

Finally, keep in mind that if you choose to turn on the Do Not Track function on your browser, we may continue to use all information we collected prior to your turning that function on, in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

**What if I have questions about this policy?**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to support@guilded.gg, and we will try to resolve your concerns.

**What if I am a European resident?**

If you are a resident of the European Union (“EU”), United Kingdom, Lichtenstein, Norway, or Iceland, you may have additional rights under the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) with respect to your Personal Data, as outlined below.

For this section, we use the terms “Personal Data” and “processing” as they are defined in the GDPR, but “Personal Data” generally means information that can be used to individually identify a person, and “processing” generally covers actions that can be performed in connection with data such as collection, use, storage and disclosure. Guilded will be the controller of your Personal Data processed in connection with the Services.

If there are any conflicts between this section and any other provision of this Privacy Policy, the policy or portion that is more protective of Personal Data shall control to the extent of such conflict. If you have any questions about this section or whether any of the following applies to you, please contact us at support@guilded.gg. Note that we may also process Personal Data of our customers’ end users or employees in connection with our provision of services to customers, in which case we are the processor of Personal Data. If we are the processor of your Personal Data (i.e., not the controller), please contact the controller party in the first instance to address your rights with respect to such data.

**What Personal Data Do We Collect From You?** We collect Personal Data about you when you provide such information directly to us, when third parties such as our business partners or service providers provide us with Personal Data about you, or when Personal Data about you is automatically collected in connection with your use of our Services.

Information we collect directly from you: As explained above, we receive Personal Data directly from you when you provide us with such Personal Data, including the following: 

*   username
    
*   email address
    
*   third-party account credentials (for example, Blizzard® BattleTag™ tag)
    
*   user profile information, including images and videos you have uploaded to the site

Information we (or our third-party service providers) automatically collect when you use our Services: The following Personal Data is automatically collected when you use our Services: 

*   IP address
    
*   chat logs

**How Do We Use Your Personal Data?** We process Personal Data to operate, improve, understand and personalize our Services. For example, we use Personal Data to: 

*   Create and manage user profiles
    
*   Communicate with you about the Services
    
*   Contact you about Service announcements, updates or offers
    
*   Provide support and assistance for the Services
    
*   Personalize website content and communications based on your preferences
    
*   Meet contract or legal obligations
    
*   Respond to user inquiries
    
*   Fulfill user requests
    
*   Comply with our legal or contractual obligations
    
*   Resolve disputes
    
*   Protect against or deter fraudulent, illegal or harmful actions
    
*   Enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/privacy)

We will only process your Personal Data if we have a lawful basis for doing so. Lawful bases for processing include consent, contractual necessity and our “legitimate interests” or the legitimate interest of others, as further described below. 

*   **Contractual Necessity:** We process the following categories of Personal Data as a matter of “contractual necessity”, meaning that we need to process the data to perform under our [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/terms) with you, which enables us to provide you with the Services. When we process data due to contractual necessity, failure to provide such Personal Data will result in your inability to use some or all portions of the Services that require such data.

*   username
    
*   email address
    
*   third-party account credentials (for example, Blizzard® BattleTag™ tag)
    
*   user profile information, including images and videos you have uploaded to the site 

*   **Legitimate Interest:** We process the following categories of Personal Data when we believe it furthers the legitimate interest of us or third parties.

*   IP address
    
*   chat logs

Examples of these legitimate interests include:

*   Operation and improvement of our business, products and services
    
*   Marketing of our products and services
    
*   Provision of customer support
    
*   Protection from fraud or security threats
    
*   Compliance with legal obligations
    
*   Completion of corporate transactions
    
*   Enforcement of our [Terms of Use](http://www.guilded.gg/about/terms) 

*   **Consent:** In some cases, we process Personal Data based on the consent you expressly grant to us at the time we collect such data. When we process Personal Data based on your consent, it will be expressly indicated to you at the point and time of collection. 

*   **Other Processing Grounds:** From time to time we may also need to process Personal Data to comply with a legal obligation, if it is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or other data subjects, or if it is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest.

**How and With Whom Do We Share Your Data?** We do not share your Personal Data with third parties except as expressly set forth below.

We share your Personal Data when necessary to complete a transaction initiated or authorized by you or provide you with a product or service you have requested—for example, we may share your Personal Data: 

*   To other users when you post information publicly on the Services; and
    
*   With third-party services, such as YouTube, third-party social media services and gaming apps and platforms, such as Blizzard® Battle.net™, if you interact with them through your use of the Services.

We may also share Personal Data when we believe it is necessary to:  

*   Comply with applicable law or respond to valid legal process, including from law enforcement or other government agencies
    
*   Protect us, our business or our users, for example to enforce our terms of service, prevent spam or other unwanted communications and investigate or protect against fraud
    
*   Maintain the security of our products and services

We also may share information with third parties when you give us consent to do so.

**How Long Do We Retain Your Personal Data?** We retain Personal Data about you for as long as you have an open account with us or as otherwise necessary to provide you Services. In some cases we retain Personal Data for longer, if doing so is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes or collect fees owed, or is otherwise permitted or required by applicable law, rule or regulation. Afterwards, we retain some information in a depersonalized or aggregated form but not in a way that would identify you personally.

**What Security Measures Do We Use?** We seek to protect Personal Data using appropriate technical and organizational measures based on the type of Personal Data and applicable processing activity. For example, sensitive user information is encrypted, and only stored when used as necessary to operate the service.

**What Rights Do You Have Regarding Your Personal Data?** You have certain rights with respect to your Personal Data, including those set forth below. For more information about these rights, or to submit a request, please email support@guilded.gg. Please note that in some circumstances, we may not be able to fully comply with your request, such as if it is frivolous or extremely impractical, if it jeopardizes the rights of others, or if it is not required by law, but in those circumstances, we will still respond to notify you of such a decision. In some cases, we may also need to you to provide us with additional information, which may include Personal Data, if necessary to verify your identity and the nature of your request. 

*   **Access****:** You can request more information about the Personal Data we hold about you and request a copy of such Personal Data. You can also access certain parts of your of your Personal Data by emailing [support@guilded.gg](http://www.guilded.gg/about/terms) and requesting that personal data.
    
*   **Rectification****:** If you believe that any Personal Data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data. You can also correct some of this information directly by editing it from your user profile on the site or by emailing support@guilded.gg.
    
*   **Erasure****:** You can request that we erase some or all of your Personal Data from our systems.
    
*   **Withdrawal of Consent****:** If we are processing your Personal Data based on your consent (as indicated at the time of collection of such data), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note, however, that if you exercise this right, you may have to then provide express consent on a case-by-case basis for the use or disclosure of certain of your Personal Data, if such use or disclosure is necessary to enable you to utilize some or all of our Services.
    
*   **Portability****:** You can ask for a copy of your Personal Data in a machine-readable format. You can also request that we transmit the data to another controller where technically feasible.
    
*   **Objection****:** You can contact us to let us know that you object to the further use or disclosure of your Personal Data for certain purposes, such as for direct marketing purposes.
    
*   **Restriction of Processing****:** You can ask us to restrict further processing of your Personal Data.
    
*   **Right to File Complaint****:** You have the right to lodge a complaint about Guilded’s practices with respect to your Personal Data with the supervisory authority of your country or EU Member State.

**What If You Have Questions Regarding Your Personal Data?** If you have any questions about this section or our data practices generally, please contact us using the following information: Name, physical address, email address for contact, and designated representative and contact information.
